socialaddworld.us.com 2019-07-30

# Welcome

We values the trust placed in us by data subject and therefore, we follow the highest standards of privacy guidelines to protect the information shared by you with us.

This privacy policy describes the usage of information provided or collected by members, which operates various Mobile applications & other services including but not limited to delivery of information and content via any mobile or internet connected device or otherwise (collectively the "Services"). We follow this privacy policy in accordance with applicable law in the places where we operate. In some cases, we may provide additional data privacy notices specific to certain services or regions. Those terms are to be read in combination with this policy. 

This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction and together with the Terms of Use applicable to the Service that you are using.

## What does this privacy policy cover?

The objective of the privacy policy is to inform you regarding the processing of your personal information which is collected during your visit to our website/application. This policy applies to current and former visitors of the website/application, users who register on Allinoneindia in connection with use of our services, or whose information otherwise receives in connection with its services. 

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information (PI) - means any information relating to an identified or identifiable living person (‘data subject’ here in referred as you/your’). In particular using a common identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. 

The Company respects the privacy of the users of the Services and is committed to reasonably protect it in all respects.
